<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data> 
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Dopo apple]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/2.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/2.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Apples have a rounded shape with a depression at the top where the stem is attached. Some apples are almost perfectly round, while others are more rounded at the top and narrower at the bottom.  In addition, some have knobby lobes at the calyx end (bottom) of the fruit.  Apple fruits are firm and the skin is shiny and smooth. The color of the skin can be red, green, yellow, or a combination of those colors. The flesh is white or ivory.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Green pear]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[pear]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/7.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/7.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Pear trees can grow to reach a height of 45 feet. They are longer lived than apple trees and generally have less disease problems; although pear trees bloom earlier in the spring and are more susceptible to frost damage.<br /><br />Pear leaves are simple, finely toothed, and glossy green in color. Their shape is oval to oblong with a short pointed tip.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Austra apple]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/3.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/3.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Apple trees can range in size from 6 to 30 feet in height, depending on the variety and type of rootstock (dwarf, semi-dwarf, etc.).<br><br>Apple trees have simple leaves that are arranged alternately along the stem. The leaves are bright to dark green in color and the margins of the leaf are toothed.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Western orange]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[orange]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/4.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/4.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[An orange—specifically, the sweet orange—is the citrus fruit Citrus sinensis (syn. Citrus aurantium L. var. dulcis L., or Citrus aurantium Risso) and its fruit. The orange is a hybrid of ancient cultivated origin, possibly between pomelo (Citrus maxima) and tangerine (Citrus reticulata). It is a small flowering tree growing to about 10 m tall with evergreen leaves, which are arranged alternately, of ovate shape with crenulate margins and 4–10 cm long. The orange fruit is a hesperidium, a type of berry.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Perfume orange]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[orange]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/5.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/5.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Oranges are oval to sphere-shaped fruits with leathery, porous skin. Their color ranges from orange to red-orange. Oranges may be confused with other citrus fruits, such as grapefruits and tangerines. However, grapefruits are usually much larger and more yellow than oranges, and tangerines have a more flattened sphere shape than oranges.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Sweet pear]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[pear]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/6.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/6.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Pears have a distinctive bell shape fruit. Some pears have knobby lobes at the base of the fruit while others are smooth at the base. The skin of the fruit ranges in color from green, yellow, red, brown, pink, or a combination of these colors.  Pear flesh is white and juicy and grainy in texture. Bartlett pears are shown in this picture.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Kascra apple]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[apple]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/1.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/1.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Apples are the most popular backyard tree fruit for this area. A number of varieties are available (see following table), with variation in time of ripening and best use (cooking, eating, or both). Scab immune (SI) varieties are resistant to apple scab disease. Plant at least two varieties to assure cross-pollination. Winesap and Turley have sterile pollen, however, so dont include it as a pollinating variety in the plan.]]></content>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title><![CDATA[Sintalias banana]]></title>
		<category><![CDATA[banana]]></category>
		<thumb><![CDATA[images/thumb/8.jpg]]></thumb>
		<fullsize><![CDATA[images/fullsize/8.jpg]]></fullsize>
		<content><![CDATA[Bananas are in the shape of a long curving cylinder. The bottom end narrows to a point and the top end has a thick stem that attaches the fruit to the inflorescence stalk.  A small group of bananas is termed "hands".  Hands are collectively known as "bunches". Banana skin is smooth and thick, and often has a few vertical ridges that run the length of the fruit. The flesh is creamy white and soft.]]></content>
	</item>
</data>